<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wokeuplukethis</title>
    <description>Hope this blog helps anyone, but for now I'm just trying to help my newbie self up.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/wokeuplukethis/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/wokeuplukethis/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 22:30:42 +0900</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 22:30:42 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.0.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Les Ambassadeurs, the first Restaurant we Visited in Paris</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Within the Hôtel de Crillon, which was built in 1758, Les Ambassadeurs operated as a restaurant since the mid-19th century. It reached its peak of fame as a restaurant and nightclub (a café-concert) in the last three decades of the 19th century.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Always a center of entertainment for the aristocracy, in the 1870s it also became a regular destination of some of the best known figures of art and the demi-monde. Edgar Degas and Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec portrayed visitors at the night club, and Aristide Bruant performed there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It was decorated in an 18th-century rococo style, redesigned by Sybille de Margérie with furnishings by Sonia Rykiel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.google.com/logos/doodles/2020/thank-you-emergency-services-workers-6753651837108755-s.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;render() {
    return (
        &amp;lt;View&amp;gt;
            &amp;lt;Text&amp;gt;
                Hello, world.
            &amp;lt;/Text&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;/View&amp;gt;
    )
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following a renovation of the hotel in 1981–85, the restaurant occupied a former private ballroom with windows looking out on the Place de la Concorde, a few hundred meters from the Palais Garnier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les Ambassadeurs had two Michelin stars. In the last decade of its operation, chef was Dominique Bouchet followed by Jean-François Piège and finally when the hotel closed in 2013 for an extended renovation, Christopher Hache.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2017 Hache opened a smaller restaurant, L’Écrin, within the renovated hotel; the former space of Les Ambassadeurs became a bar.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/wokeuplukethis/les-ambassadeurs/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/wokeuplukethis/les-ambassadeurs/</guid>
        
        <category>France</category>
        
        
        <category>Lifestyle</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
